把她弄成黑白的  其他的保持彩色
Make her black and white, everything else in color.
艾丽西娅写给威尔
Alicia to Will:
这周你出差了
"You were away at depos this week
我的脑海中全是你的手抚摸着我
All I could think about is your hands on me."
有时候觉得这很危险
Sometimes this feels too dangerous.
编辑室
Editing.
你最好出去看看
You'd better get out there.
她在计划使用那些非法取得的邮件
She is planning to use illegally obtained e-mails.
不只是使用而已  还想传播出去
Not just use-- broadcast.
这种做法已经违反了法律
Which is so far beyond the pale,
我不敢相信我们居然在谈论这种事情
I can't believe we're having this conversation.
我没有黑她的邮件
I-I didn't hack her e-mails--
我只是收到了这些邮件的副本
I just received copies of them.
-这有什么区别  -区别可大了
- A distinction without a difference. - Well, no.
最高法院对此做出过裁定
The Supreme Court has spoken to this.